

Profile

A self-motivated, multifaceted, electronics engineering undergraduate, who has gained experience in various fields of endeavor, such as physical sciences, programming, audio and video processing, marketing, electronics engineering, and has a broad understanding of the co-operate world and it's work ethics

Contact

- ★ Lippstadt 59555
- **L** +49 15217833741

DAMILOLA AWOSURU

Education

BACHELOR'S IN ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING

Hochschule Hamm-Lippstadt, Lippstadt | 09/2019 - Present

Competencies to understand challenges in the field of autonomous systems and competencies in the field of hardware and software codesign techniques up to design, as well as analysis techniques for mechatronic and time-critical systems.

Experience

STUDENT ASSISTANT

Hochschule Hamm-Lippstadt | 09/2021 - Present Assisting my professor in research and projects.

IT PROBLEM SOLVE

Amazon | 10/2020 - 12/2020

Task was to deal with problems in the areas of supply chain management, with the help of various specified Unix and web based tools, for the continuous flow of operations.

Employer: Amazon.

FINANCE INTERN

Communication Concepts | 01/2019 - 03/2019

Part of the team responsible for the soliciting of funds and generation of revenue for the Non-Governmental Organisation.
Employer: Anat Abiola

DATA ANALYST INTERN

PowerSoft Technologies | 01/2017 - 02/2017

Performed a variety of data-based tasks, such as data capturing, modelling and organisation, that support decision making in the company.

Employer: Femi Ojo.

Skills

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Python
Java
C
C++
MATLAB
Arduino

PERSONAL SKILLS

Critical thinking Problem solving Resourcefulness Leadership Team player Ingenuity



SOFTWARE SKILLS

LATEX
SolidWorks
Microsoft Office
Adobe Illustrator
Buildbox
Citavi

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English German



Training Courses

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION LEARNING ARDUNIO

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION LEARNING MATLAB

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION LEARNING SOLIDWORKS

Volunteer work

FOOD DRIVE

Participated in a food drive for impoverished children in impoverished communities.

RELIEF ITEMS

Donated for the distribution of relief items to those who can no longer provide for themselves and family because of the lock-down due to the corona-virus pandemic.

TRAINING

Member of an NGO that offers environmental sustainability training to government officials in Nigeria.

Membership

ARBEITER-SMARITER-BUND (SASB)

RED CROSS

Interests

TECHNOLOGY

MATHEMATICS

ENCYCLOPEDIAS

MUSIC

Links



GitHub

https://github.com/dami-caleb

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/damilola-caleb-awosuru-2826331a2